♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Live from New York City,
it's the JCPenney
Thanksgiving Day Parade.
The JCPenney parade?
Yeah, it's like
the Macy's parade,
only without
licensed characters.
With the popular
balloons we all know and love--
Mickey Rabbit,
Sponge Cow,
and Clifton the Small Blue Dog.
Peter, get in here!
You want to tell me
what the hell happened
to our Thanksgiving turkey?
Oh, that.
Uh, well, last night,
Brian and I
got drunk and
ate the turkey.
But before you get mad,
we also ate the salad.
Damn it, how could
you guys do that?!
Boy, I must have
been really drunk.
I don't remember
any of that.
No problem.
Instagram
remembers for you.
Peter, we've got a houseful
of people coming
and they're
expecting a turkey.
Well, if they're
expecting a turkey,
I'll just put on
Evan Almighty for them.
Zap!
You and Brian better get
another turkey right now!
And don't bother
coming back until you do!
Don't worry, Lois.
We will.
Yeah, we'll be back
with a turkey
faster than you can
say, "Jack Robinson."
Jack Rober...
Jack Row...
She had a stroke that killed
the part of her brain
that says "Jack Robinson."
We got plenty of time.
All right, Brian,
first order of business--
we have to decide
who gets to ride in the cart
and who has to push it.
Well, I'm smaller, so...
The decision
has been made.
Ooh, now I want that one.
Aw, crap-- looks like
they're completely sold out.
Yeah, sorry.
We just sold our last
turkey to that guy.
You are the turkey
I have chosen to pardon.
Fly free, turkey!
Oh, Fudgsicles!
Hey, you don't sell
turkeys here, do you?
We've been to every grocery
store in town with no luck.
are these little packets
of weird vitamins
that vaguely suggest
they help you in the bedroom.
"Performance and
stamina, for men."
I know what that means.
Peter, enough.
Come to bed.
Uh-uh, Lois.
The packet says I got to
play till I'm raw.
Can't believe
every turkey
within a 60-mile radius
of Quahog is sold out.
I know. And now
we're so far from home,
none of your
stations even work.
♪ She thinks I'm beautiful ♪
♪ Meet Virginia ♪
Is this...
Is this fine?
I mean, it's
not... it's...
Yeah, it's fine if
you think it's fine.
It's not that good
of a song, but we know it.
Yeah, okay. Sure.
♪ She never compromises... ♪
Brian, I love Train.
I  love Train.
Chris, are Brian and
your father back yet?
No. And why are you saying
the dog's name before Dad's?
It's weird.
That is weird, you're right.
Well, they better
get here soon.
I can't host this
Thanksgiving dinner on my own.
Hear that?
This thing's all on you.
What? What are you
talking about?
Well, the fat man's never
going to get back in time,
and with him gone, that makes
you the man of the house.
I sentence you to death!
Chris, Chris, slow down.
I'm just saying,
without Peter here,
you're going to have to be
the host of Thanksgiving.
You have to do everything
the fat man normally would.
You mean, like,
fall asleep on the toilet
and have a big red ring
on my bum for a week?
No, no, no-- greeting
guests as they arrive.
Facilitating small talk.
And, of course, giving
the Thanksgiving toast.
Boy, yesterday I'm
microwaving a cat,
today I'm giving
a speech.
Things move fast
around here.
Hi, do you have any turkeys?
Sure do.
You're looking at one.
I'm sorry.
You have to know me
to know I'm just joking.
Sir, the day we've had,
we could use
a good chuckle like that.
You folks are in luck.
Looks like we have
one turkey left.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, you're telling me.
We didn't come back
with a turkey,
Lois would be madder than
that time she got a Capp smear.
All right, we're just going
to take a quick Capp smear.
Don't you mean
pap smear?
No, at this hospital
we obtain the sample
using beloved British comic
strip roustabout Andy Capp.
'Ello, luv.
Let's have a smear.
I'm not letting
you do that.
You can't even see.
That's all right, bird.
I goes by smell.
Brian, look,
an eight-foot basket.
Let me just dunk
the turkey once.
I know I can jam it.
That's not
a regulation rim.
Okay, you know what?
I'm in charge of the turkey.
You're driving.
This thing on?
Yes.
It's not making
any noise.
It's a hybrid.
Trust me, it's on.
No, it's not. See?
Oh, my God!
Not now! Not like this!
Peter, what the hell?!
You chose
a turkey over me?!
I almost died!
I swear to God, I thought
dogs could breathe underwater.
Great. The water completely
killed my phone.
Oh, horrors.
You have to spend
time with me
without looking
at your phone.
Here, give me yours.
I threw mine
at a duck.
Excuse me, can you help us?
We're trying to get
back to Quahog.
If you want, I can take you
as far as the bus station.
You can?
Oh, thank you so much!
Oh, that is the nicest thing
anyone's done for me
since my kids gave me
that Father's Day gift.
Oh, look, a tie.
Perfect.
It's from all of us!
All right, Chris,
acting as host
will demand a higher
level of conversation.
I suggest
as your opener--
"Lois, everything
is delicious."
Then that's
what I will say.
Unless Slender Man
commands me
to say something else.
Ugh, this is gonna be
a bigger disaster than Y2-Gay.
Three! Two! One!
I hope my dad's
not watching ABC!
Oh, thank God
we got on this bus.
I really had to poop.
Wait, where is there
a bathroom on this bus?
I didn't say there
was a bathroom,
I just said
I had to poop.
Oh, my God!
This is gross
even for a bus!
I don't know what
they were so mad about,
I did it in
a Rite Aid bag.
Damn it, Peter!
That was our only way home!
Well, that's where
you're wrong, Brian.
Free bus bike!
Aw, crap, this
is a girl's bike.
All right,
we'll ride it,
but pray to God nobody
from school sees us.
Nice bike, butt-munch!
Shut up!
I'm telling Miss Baumbakis!
Up next on Nickelodeon,
Uncomfortably Hot
Eighteen-Year-Old Girls.
Honey, where
are you off to?
To the car wash
to raise money for our
new soccer uniforms.
Okay, have fun.
Nickelodeon--
casually ask your daughter
what that girl's name is,
then take your laptop
into the bathroom.
Uh, Mom! Daddy!
You're right on time!
Happy Thanksgiving,
dear!
We brought some wine,
but it's good wine
so it's just or us.
Damn it. Where the hell
are they with that turkey?
Hi, you've reached Brian Griffin
of The Write Stuff
writing classes...
Oh, God.
Come on,
keep pedaling.
Dinner starts in an hour.
Oh! Ow!
Damn it, Peter!
Oh, great.
You broke the chain
and now we have to walk!
Unless we hitchhike.
Hitchhike? You know
how dangerous that is?
Besides, we're in
the middle of nowhere.
There aren't even
any cars around.
There's one.
Hey! Hey, stop!
Give us a ride!
It's just me and my upright dog.
We're obviously not weirdoes!
See, Brian? Told ya.
We're going to be home
in no time.
Hi there, folks.
Hand over the turkey.
What?!
I can't go back to my wife
without a turkey!
Oh, yeah?
Bet that thing's
not even loaded.
You just used
your last bullet.
Running on empty now.
Brian, give him the turkey.
Okay, buddy, you ready to
test out those hosting skills?
Now go wow your guests
with conversation.
Hi, Grandma.
I got some down-there
hair now-- want to see?
Uh, I-I...
I should check if your mother
needs help in the kitchen.
Sometimes I pluck them
because I deserve pain.
Cut! No. Stop.
I'm sorry! I panicked!
It's all right. It's okay.
Don't worry, Chris.
You can't always get things
right on the first try.
Just look at Snoopy's
original happy dance.
Hey, you having
a good time tonight?
Oh, yeah.
Can't believe
we got robbed.
Yeah, but can we just
talk for a second
about how brave I was when
we walked past that cemetery?
Peter, do you not see that we
are completely screwed here?
And it's all
thanks to you!
You drove my car into a lake,
you almost let me drown,
you got us thrown off a bus,
you broke our bike,
and now you've gotten
our turkey stolen
and Thanksgiving
is ruined
and we don't have
any transportation
and we're still
miles from home!
You're starting to get
black gums like an older dog.
You know what? You know what?
Maybe it's my fault.
I forgot, I'm talking
to a complete idiot.
You are so stupid!
Oh, yeah?
Well, if I'm so stupid,
then how did I manage to
frame you for eating the turkey?
What?!
Yeah!
Didn't you notice you were
passed out in all those photos?
You didn't eat any of it.
I just posed you like that
because I didn't want
to take all the blame.
You son of a bitch!
How could you do that to me?
You're a dog, Brian.
I can throw you
off a bridge,
and as long as I don't hit
a person on a boat, it's okay.
Screw this. I am done!
This isn't even my problem,
it's your problem.
You know what, Peter?
You've got no turkey,
and now you've got no friend.
Good-bye!
W-Wait-- Brian, wait!
♪ Now let's watch
a whole bunch of ads. ♪
Nice Thanksgiving.
I don't know why I ever listen
to that jerk.
What?
Home is this way;
we're both just walking home.
Leave me alone!
No way. We're a team, Brian,
whether you like it or not.
Just like almond butter
and no sugar added
fruit preserves.
Who's hungry?
We are!
Hey, kids, would you like
a terrible healthy sandwich?
No.
Too bad, because
your recently divorced mom
has a crush on her trainer,
and he eats like this,
so now you have to, too.
Almond butter and no sugar
added fruit preserves--
just like PB and J,
but with more
of your mom railing this guy.
I named myself Kaya!
We stopped being a team
when you framed me for eating
that turkey with you.
Brian, maybe you should be
a little less mad at me
and a little more mad
at the guys
growing mustaches
for this month.
Hey, don't mock
Mo-vember.
Last year, I raised
eight dollars
and got on
a BuzzFeed listicle.
No! You use real words!
Internet stuff
is not real words.
Hey, look!
There's our answer.
We break into the zoo,
steal a turkey,
bring it home, we're heroes.
Peter, stop it!
You're gonna
get yourself hurt.
Sorry, can't hear you.
Too busy saving
our family's Thanksgiving.
Damn it.
This is idiotic.
You're never gonna find
a turkey in there.
Oh, I'll find one.
I mean, you're
looking at the guy
who found the
Fountain of Youth.
It's very far
away from here!
Hey, Lois,
thanks for letting Kevin
bring his girlfriend
this year.
And I hope it's not awkward
that she's a little person
and they viciously fight
all the time.
Why do we have to spend every
holiday with your family?
Shut up!
I'm a full-size person!
I make the decisions!
Don't you worry.
This'll quickly turn
into rough,
front-yard, makeup sex.
All this fighting is
making me so damn hot.
Oh, my God.
It looks like he's
chalking a pool cue.
Hey, scoot over.
As the oldest guy here,
it's my duty to take
an open mouth nap
in the middle of the room.
God, look at my mom.
Dinner should've been served
half an hour ago.
She's clearly stalling
for time.
Okay, everybody.
Dinner's gonna be ready
very soon.
Uh, what?
Um, oh, good.
But before we get started,
I thought we could all take
turns telling a long story
about how things aren't
the way they used to be.
Daddy, would you care
to start?
You bet I would.
Too much candy!
Too much candy?
What do you mean,
too much candy?
There's too much candy!
There used to be four candies.
Bulls-eyes, Yahoos,
Sweet Yarn and cigarettes.
Now I go into a store,
I don't know whether
I'm coming or going!
Is there anything else?
Why don't ballplayers wear
giant woolen shirts anymore?
What's wrong with wool?
It was a perfect fabric.
You go to the ballpark,
get your bag of Bulls-eyes
and watch Hack Wilson round
the bases in a big wool shirt.
I once saw Hack hit a ball
out of the infield.
I still remember
the thud of the bat
and the whoosh of the wool.
I wish things were still heavy.
Oh, the rails are
off this thing.
All right, Chris,
this is where you, as host,
need to step in and...
Chris? Chris?
What the hell?
Are you drunk?
I couldn't handle
the pressure, Stewie.
We Irish,
we have a deep sadness.
Oh, come on, get up!
They need you down there.
♪ Too-Ra-loo-Ra-loo-ral. ♪
All right, there they are.
I'm going in and getting
us a turkey, Brian.
Hey, buddy, you want
to come to my house
so my wife can cook you wrong?
Ah, damn it!
Peter, this is never gonna work.
All right,
just leave the turkey alone.
The poor thing is... Aah! Aah!
What the hell?!
Knock it off!
Ow! Damn it, I'm gonna
kill you, you dick!
Quick, Brian,
it's getting away!
Where'd he go?
He's not in here.
Over there!
Oh, crap.
Easy there.
Hey, it's Thanksgiving.
Shouldn't you be in Detroit
losing a football game
right now?
Brian, up here!
Oh, my God.
Thank you, Peter.
Thank you so much!
Hey, you're welcome, buddy.
You...
You saved my life.
Of course I did.
You're my best friend.
Hey, listen, I'm-I'm...
I'm sorry I messed
everything up today.
It's okay.
I guess I've been
kind of a jerk, too.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
Ah, I deserved it.
I mean, for God's sake,
I sank your car in a lake.
And I broke
this guy's neck just now.
Yeesh.
But, hey, we cut the legs
off him and dye him brown,
we got ourselves
a turkey, right?
No. We've come this far.
Let's do it right.
Hey, you got a tiny head
and a big body.
What if I switched that?
Gotcha!
All right, we did it!
We got ourselves a turkey.
Yeah, but what
time is it?
I mean, dinner has to
have started by now.
We're never gonna make
it home on foot.
Maybe we don't have to.
We're now arriving in Quahog.
Up on the right are the people
with the awesome trampoline,
but they don't let me
on it no more,
'cause I bounced a kid
onto the house.
There were no
squeezable condiments.
Ketchup came in a can.
And, Daddy, what about the pants
that kids today are wearing?
Are they properly sized?
Are we gonna eat soon?
I have an interesting factoid
about what makes you
sleepy afterwards.
Yeah, the hell with this.
I'm starving.
Okay, I guess we should eat.
Well, obviously
Peter's not here.
So it's fallen to me
to take up the mantle.
Now, I wasn't planning on
doing this today,
but when I look around at all
of these open, loving faces
or friends and family,
I am comfortable enough
to finally say
that I am a proud,
unashamed, active...
Lois, we're home
and Thanksgiving is saved!
Kidding!
Oh, my God, where the
hell have you been?
And what are you doing
with a live turkey?!
A live turkey
who loves Rollerblading.
Our dog drew that.
Peter, we can't eat
a live turkey.
Look, Lois, I still got time
to make this right.
And I'm gonna.
Hand me a nine iron
and show me to the backyard.
Well, buddy, I guess this is it.
Aah! Aah!
Wow, I-I...
I read that look wrong.
Ah, geez, I'm sorry.
I wish you didn't have to die,
but a bunch of white people
put on sweaters.
I couldn't do it.
What?
I'm sorry, Lois.
I know you wanted the
perfect Thanksgiving,
and I know I screwed
that all up for you,
but when you
think about it,
isn't this holiday about
being with people you love?
I mean, does it really matter
what we eat?
What matters
is we're all together.
Family and friends.
And one new friend.
Oh, Peter, that's beautiful.
Lois, can the turkey please
join us for dinner?
Not as the meal,
but as our guest?
Of course he can.
Happy Thanksgiving, everyone.
The man of the house
killed a turkey
for Thanksgiving!
Well, looks like we're
having turkey after all.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
Four years later, me and Lois
divorced and Stewie died.
Gobble, gobble!